Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0952, 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0952)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0953, 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0953)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0954, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0954)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0955, 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0955)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0956, 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0956)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0957, 1 fragment 03.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0957)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0958, 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0958)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0959, 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0959)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0960, 1 fragment 04.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0960)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0961, 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 22, Item P.NYU inv 0961)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0962, 1 fragment 05.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0962)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0963, 1 fragment 05.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0963)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0964, 1 fragment 03.5 x 11.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0964)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0965, 1 fragment 07.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0965)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0966, 1 fragment 06.5 x 15.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0966)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0967, 1 fragment 13.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0967)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0968, 1 fragment 06.0 x 19.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0968)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0969, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0969)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0970, 1 fragment 08.0 x 21.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0970)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0971, 1 fragment 08.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0971)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0972, 1 fragment 08.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0972)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0973, 1 fragment 05.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0973)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0974, 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0974)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0975, 1 fragment 15.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0975)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0976, 1 fragment 08.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0976)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0977, 1 fragment 06.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0977)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0978, 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0978)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0979, 1 fragment 08.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0979)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0980, 1 fragment 05.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0980)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0981, 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0981)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0982, 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0982)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0983, 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0983)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0984.01, 1 fragment 02.0 x 00.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0984.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0984.02, 1 fragment 00.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0984.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0984.03, 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0984.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0985, 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0985)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0986, 1 fragment 31.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0986)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0987, 1 fragment 13.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0987)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0988, 1 fragment 06.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0988)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0989, 1 fragment 03.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0989)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0990, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0990)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0991, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0991)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0992, 1 fragment 09.5 x 16.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0992)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0993, 1 fragment 04.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0993)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0994, 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0994)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0995, 1 fragment 06.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0995)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0996, 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0996)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0997, 1 fragment 12.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0997)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0998, 1 fragment 03.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 0998)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1000, 1 fragment 04.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1000)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1001, 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1001)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1002, 1 fragment 12.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1002)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1003, 1 fragment 06.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1003)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1004, 1 fragment 07.5 x 14.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1004)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1005, 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1005)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1006, 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1006)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1007, 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1007)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1008, 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1008)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1009, 1 fragment 06.0 x 17.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1009)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1010, 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1010)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1011, 1 fragment 06.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1011)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1012, 1 fragment 08.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1012)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1013, 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1013)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1014, 1 fragment 06.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1014)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1015, 1 fragment 18.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1015)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1016, 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1016)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1018, 1 fragment 11.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1018)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1019, 1 fragment 04.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1019)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1020, 1 fragment 03.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1020)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1021, 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1021)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1022, 1 fragment 03.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1022)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1023, 1 fragment 07.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1023)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1024, 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1024)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1025, 1 fragment 07.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 23, Item P.NYU inv 1025)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1026, 1 fragment 02.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1026)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1027, 1 fragment 18.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1027)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1028.01, 1 fragment 06.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1028.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1028.02, 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1028.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1029, 1 fragment 01.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1029)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1030, 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1030)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1031, 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1031)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1032, 1 fragment 07.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1032)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1033, 1 fragment 03.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1033)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1034, 1 fragment 04.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1034)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1035, 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1035)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1036, 1 fragment 09.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1036)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1037, 1 fragment 07.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1037)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1038, 1 fragment 03.5 x 13.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1038)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1039, 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1039)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1040, 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1040)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1041, 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1041)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1042, 1 fragment 09.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1042)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1043, 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1043)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1044, 1 fragment 02.0 x 00.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1044)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1045, 1 fragment 02.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1045)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1046, 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1046)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1047, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1047)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1048, 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1048)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1049, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1049)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1050, 1 fragment 07.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1050)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1051, 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1051)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1052, 1 fragment 06.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1052)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1053, 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1053)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1054, 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1054)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1055, 1 fragment 11.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1055)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1056, 1 fragment 02.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1056)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1057, 1 fragment 01.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1057)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1058, 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1058)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1059, 1 fragment 05.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1059)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1060, 1 fragment 02.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1060)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1061, 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1061)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1062, 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1062)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1063, 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1063)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1064, 1 fragment 00.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1064)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1065, 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1065)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1066, 1 fragment 01.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1066)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1067, 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1067)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1068, 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1068)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1069, 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1069)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1070, 1 fragment 00.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1070)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1071, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1071)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1072, 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1072)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1073, 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1073)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1077, 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1077)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1078, 1 fragment 06.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1078)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1079, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1079)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1081, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1081)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1082, 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1082)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1083, 1 fragment 06.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1083)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1084, 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1084)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1085, 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1085)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1086, 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1086)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1087, 1 fragment 09.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1087)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1088, 1 fragment 12.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1088)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1089, 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 24, Item P.NYU inv 1089)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1090, 1 fragment 14.5 x 15.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1090)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1091.01, 1 fragment 08.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1091.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1091.02, 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1091.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1094, 1 fragment 04.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1094)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1095, 1 fragment 04.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1095)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1096, 1 fragment 06.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1096)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1097, 1 fragment 07.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1097)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1098, 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1098)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1099, 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1099)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1100, 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1100)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1101, 1 fragment 04.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1101)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1102, 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1102)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1103, 1 fragment 06.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1103)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1104, 1 fragment 04.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1104)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1105, 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1105)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1106, 1 fragment 00.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1106)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1107, 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1107)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1108, 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1108)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1109, 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1109)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1110, 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1110)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1111, 1 fragment 04.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1111)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1112, 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1112)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1113, 1 fragment 07.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1113)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1114, 1 fragment 08.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1114)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1115, 1 fragment 10.0 x 16.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1115)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1116, 1 fragment 09.5 x 13.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1116)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1117, 1 fragment 11.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1117)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1118, 1 fragment 10.0 x 13.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1118)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1119, 1 fragment 10.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1119)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1120, 1 fragment 10.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1120)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1121, 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1121)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1122, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1122)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1123, 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1123)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1124, 1 fragment 05.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1124)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1125, 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1125)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1126, 1 fragment 02.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1126)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1127, 1 fragment 03.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1127)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1128, 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1128)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1129, 1 fragment 07.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1129)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1130, 1 fragment 10.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1130)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1131, 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1131)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1132, 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1132)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1133, 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1133)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1134, 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1134)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1135, 1 fragment 03.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1135)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1136, 1 fragment 09.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1136)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1137, 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1137)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1140, 1 fragment 00.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1140)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1143, 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1143)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1144, 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1144)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1145, 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1145)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1146, 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1146)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1147, 1 fragment 07.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1147)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1148, 1 fragment 04.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1148)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1149.01, 1 fragment 01.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1149.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1149.02, 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1149.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1150, 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1150)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1151, 1 fragment 05.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1151)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1152, 1 fragment 05.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1152)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1153, 1 fragment 05.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1153)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1154, 1 fragment 01.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1154)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1155, 1 fragment 02.5 x 11.5 cm (Box 25, Item P.NYU inv 1155)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1156, 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1156)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1157, 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1157)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1158, 1 fragment 02.5 x 00.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1158)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1159, 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1159)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1161, 1 fragment 07.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1161)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1162, 1 fragment 17.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1162)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1163, 1 fragment 02.0 x 13.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1163)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1164, 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1164)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1165, 1 fragment 05.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1165)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1166, 1 fragment 02.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1166)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1167, 1 fragment 04.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1167)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1168, 1 fragment 06.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1168)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1169, 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1169)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1170, 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1170)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1171, 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1171)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1172, 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1172)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1173, 1 fragment 08.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1173)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1174, 1 fragment 06.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1174)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1175, 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1175)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1176, 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1176)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1177, 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1177)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1178, 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1178)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1179, 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1179)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1180, 1 fragment 06.5 x 12.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1180)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1181, 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1181)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1182, 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1182)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1183, 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1183)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1184, 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1184)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1185, 1 fragment 00.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1185)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1186, 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1186)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1189.01, 1 fragment 02.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1189.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1189.02, 1 fragment 01.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1189.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1189.03, 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1189.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1190, 1 fragment 12.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1190)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1191, 1 fragment 07.0 x 14.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1191)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1192, 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1192)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1193, 1 fragment 03.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1193)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1194, 1 fragment 03.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1194)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1195, 1 fragment 06.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1195)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1196, 1 fragment 05.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1196)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1197, 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1197)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1198, 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1198)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1199, 1 fragment 05.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1199)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1200, 1 fragment 05.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1200)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1201, 1 fragment 10.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1201)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1202, 1 fragment 06.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1202)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1203, 1 fragment 09.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1203)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1204, 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1204)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1205, 1 fragment 06.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1205)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1206, 1 fragment 03.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1206)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1207, 1 fragment 05.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1207)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1208, 1 fragment 06.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1208)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1209, 1 fragment 07.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1209)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1210, 1 fragment 05.0 x 00.5 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1210)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1211, 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 26, Item P.NYU inv 1211)